The legend is alive!
Bigfoot is a horror, science fiction, adventure film directed by Bruce Davison.
A rock concert awakens the legendary monster, who goes on a rampage.
The event's organizer plans to kill the beast and create a tourist attraction around its stuffed body, but an environmentalist
realizes the creature is the last of its species, and is determined to make sure it does not become extinct.
Simon Quint, played by Barry Williams.
Mayor Tommy Gillis, played by Howard Hesseman.
Sheriff Becky Alvarez, played by Sherilyn Fenn.
Harley Anderson, played by Danny Bonaduce.
Alice Cooper, played by Alice Cooper.
Sheriff Walt Henderson, played by Bruce Davison.
Bigfoot (in China as King Kong 3) is a 2012 American action
adventure film produced by Asylum and Syfy.
The film was directed by Bruce Davison who also stars as a local sheriff.
It premiered on TV on June 30, 2012 and was released
on DVD and Blu-ray on August 14, 2012.
The film features a cameo by Alice Cooper playing himself.
It is unrelated to the 1970 film of the same name.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.